好吧 我们需要找到与这次调查有关的
Well, we need to locate all written information
所有的书面信息
relevant to this investigation.
你是否知道 有任何文件被销毁
Are you aware of any document destruction?
翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
字　　幕　　侠
你知道吗 我真的需要去上个洗手间
You know what? I really need to pee!
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
ZIMUXIA.CN
现在 每一次股东投票我他妈都要战斗
I'm gonna have to fight now for every fucking shareholder vote.
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　iiichiii
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
压制　Jason肖
他妈的垃圾首席运营官
Coochie-fucking-coo.
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
是啊 我已经有段时间没看到他这样了
Yeah, I haven't seen him like this for a while.
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
你想留下来过夜还是怎么
You wanna stay over or what?
难道现在不正是时候让他知道
Isn't now the time to just let him know
你有别的选项吗
you have options?
我碰巧知道有一家媒体运营
I happen to know there's a media operation
需要一个新总裁
in need of a new CEO.
我去皮尔斯吗
Me? At Pierce?
你看到这个了吗
Have you seen this?
他们说你打了他 实际上 这导致
They're saying you punched him, which caused him, in effect,
他将汽车驶进河里
to drive his car into the river.
我们去拜访一下那家人 怎么样
How about we offer a visit to the family?
实际上 肯 不如你跟我一起进去
Actually, Ken, why don't you come in with me?
我们应该在这件事上团结一致
We should stick together on this.
你不同意吗
Don't you agree?
爸 我还是要问 还是我吗
Dad? I need to ask, is it still me?
你知道我想要这个位置 而且我可以做到
You know that I want this, and that I can do it.
那你为什么要耍我
Then why are you fucking me about?
皮尔斯的职位
The Pierce job.
嘿 肯 我觉得我们有麻烦了
Hey, Ken. I think we've got a problem.
继     承
第 二 季  第８集
我们想感谢大家 来参加威拉的"宝宝"的
We want to thank you for coming to this first preview
第一次试映
of Willa's baby,
毕竟 在几千人面前...
'cause it isn't easy to...
"生孩子"真的不容易
to give birth in front of a thousand people.
所以...无论如何
So... anyway.
...但是我...我不得不说 我可以...
...But I-- I have to say, I could...
看一整天都不厌烦
watch it all day.
如果你要和你的朋友谈这个
And if you're talking with your friends,
请记住 你听到的很多台词都是占位符
remember, a lot of the lines you heard were placeholders.
-对吧  -是的 是的 嗯...
-Correct? -That's right, yeah, um...
我...我的电脑感染了病毒 所以...
I-- I had a virus, so...
是的 我觉得
Yeah, I think it's like,
如果我的台词齐全的话
maybe 30, 40 percent improvement
可以提高30％或40％的...表现
when-- if I, you know, get to full... power.
嗯 但是演员阵容 很棒
Yeah, but the cast, amazing.
绝对的
Absolutely.
不过 这只是试映 所以 你知道的 拭目以待
But previews, so, you know, watch this space.
-谢谢 谢谢  -谢谢大家
-Thank-- Thank you. -Thank you.
-我操  -你还好吗
- Fuck. -You okay?
嗯 只是瑞亚 她就像他妈的杂草
Yeah, just Rhea. She's like fucking knotweed.
爸爸揭匾的那件事
Dad's plaque thing.
是的 敦提小晚餐
Yeah, the little Dundee dinner.
飞去苏格兰 从业50周年纪念
Trip to Scotland, 50 years in the biz.
是的 不再是小晚餐了 她继搞大了
Yeah, not so little anymore. She went full on.
她正在把这变成一场他妈的惊喜派对
She's turning it into a fucking surprise party,
瑞亚制造的洛根马拉松
Rhea-produced Logan-athon.
我会告诉你爸 她是个不忠诚的阴险小人
I would tell your dad that she's a traitorous viper
她在你背后捅刀子
and that she stabbed you in the back.
得了吧
Come on.
去向洛根发牢骚吗
Go whining to Logan?
拜托 我得比这更聪明点才行
Come-- I need to be smarter than that.
那是哪位
Who's that?
那是..."他"吗
Is that... "him"?
-什么他  -"什么他"
-Him who? -"Him who?"
看看你
Look at you.
-怎么了   -你在流汗吗
-What? . -Are you sweating?
没有
No.
这是建筑用砂
It's construction sand,
本来应该是沙漠沙才对
and it's supposed to be desert sand.
-我是说 可以搞定这个问题吗  -当然
-I mean, can we fix that? -Sure.
威拉 嘿
Willa. Hey.
-你好  -我只是想祝贺你
-Hi. -I just want to say congrats.
我完全没想到 你知道吗 你...
I didn't realize, but that was, you know?
你是个剧作家
You're a playwright.
-谢谢 嗯...  -是啊
-Thank you. Yeah... -Yeah.
我的意思是 我一直告诉你 我是个剧作家
I mean, I've always told you I'm a playwright.
是的 但是 你知道 罗曼 就像...
Yeah, but, you know, Roman's, like...
"写了个剧本"
"written a screenplay."
-谢了 弟弟   -嗯 嗯
-Thanks, bro. -Yeah. Yeah.
这是最糟糕的情况 只会越来越好
This is the worst it'll be. It can only get better.
嗯 好吧
Right, okay.
嘿 那 老康 那个 那个人...
Hey, so, Con, who-- who's, um...
正在和威拉说话的那个小妞是谁
Who's that chick that Willa's talking to right now?
詹妮弗吗 噢 她是他们中的一员
Jennifer? Yeah, she's one of 'em.
她是其中一个怪咖 那些演员...
She's one of the wackjobs, the actors...
不过 是的 她太棒了
but no, yeah, she's fantastic.
她只是拥有这个令人难以置信的天赋...
She's just got this unbelievable gift for...
-伪装的天赋  -她很棒
-pretending. -She was amazing.
你还好吗
You okay?
嘿 我现在沉迷女色 所有的妞都想上
Hey, I'm drowning in pussy and everything's golden.
嗯 这很好 小肯
Well, that's great, Kenny.
-肯  -嗯
-Ken. -Yeah.
你收到瑞亚发来的关于致敬视频的邮件了吗
Did you get this email from Rhea about the tribute videos?
你知道她正在...
Yeah, and you know that she's--
她正在和悉德和莱尔德共进午餐 对吗
she's lunching Sid and Laird, right?
我的意思是...
I mean...
小西 听着 情况一直在变化...
Shiv, look. It's all changing all the time--
-好的 所以 就像 你已经退出游戏...  -所以 没什么大不了的
- Okay. So, you're like-- you're out of the game... -So, like, no big deal.
...你只是在贮藏小扁豆...
...and you're just stockpiling lentils and--
-囤积抗生素吗  -不 我不是这个意思
-and hoarding antibiotics? -No, that's not what I'm saying.
我只是说 一切都很好 懂吗
I'm just saying it's all good, you know?
就像太阳底下没什么新鲜事
It's like there's nothing new under the sun.
不好意思 我先失陪一下
Sorry, will you excuse me for just a moment?
我父亲一直是我心目中最伟大的冠军
My father has always been my greatest champion
和我的英雄
and my hero.
祝贺从业50周年 并一直处于行业巅峰
Congratulations on 50 years at the top of the biz.
我爱你 爸爸
I love you, Dad.
很好 ...你想再试一次吗
Nice....You want to try one more?
为什么
Why?
没什么 刚刚很完美 只是...
No, that was perfect, just...
不知道你是不是 是不是 想再来一次
didn't know if-- if you-- you wanted one more.
如果很完美了 我干嘛还要再来一次
If it was perfect, why would I want one more?
我只是 我的意思是 嗯...
I just-- I meant, um...
不如我们再来一次...
Why don't we do just one more where...
表现得好像你真的在抒发你的真情实感
maybe you really, like, sell how-- how you're feeling?
嗯 好吧 我们来吧
Yeah. Okay. Let's do it.
好了 第四次
All right. Take four.
怎么了 你这混蛋
What up, prick licks?
是我啊 傻逼博士
It's me, Dr. Moron.
我是叮叮当当的嘟嘟虫 有一根老鼠鸡巴
I'm a ding-dong, doodle-bug dipshit with a tit mouse dick
我爸讨厌你们所有人
and my dad hates all of you.
去你妈的 再见 怎么样
Fucky-go-bye-bye. How was that?
刚刚这样行吗
Was that good?
真有趣 爸爸居然同意
It's interesting that Dad's agreed
回苏格兰去参加这个致敬晚宴
to go back to Scotland for this dedication dinner.
他过得并不轻松
He didn't have it easy.
他不得不在外面拉屎 对吧
He had to shit outside, right?
有时候 我觉得我永远不会真正了解爸
Sometimes, I think I'll never truly understand Dad
直到我在外面拉屎
until I shit outside.
我很怀疑 蹲在排水沟上面拉屎
I doubt that squatting over a storm drain
就能真正了解他
is going to crack the case on him.
我只是说"我爱你 爸爸" 连续说了十次
I just said, "I love you, Dad," like ten times in a row.
我觉得这是我一辈子说的数量的两倍
I think that doubles my lifetime count.
嘿 你怎么看 罗曼 老爸睡瑞亚这事
Hey, what do you reckon, Rome, Dad boning Rhea?
理解不了这事
Can't wrap my head around that.
太迷雾了 太烫了
Too steamy. Too hot.
我们都应该谈谈这对我们...
We should all talk about what this means...
意味着什么 你知道吗
for us, you know?
我们...你知道吗 我们都感知到转变了 对吗
We're-- You know, we're all sensing a shift, right?
好吧 格丽说她看起来像新宠
Well, Gerri says she looks like the new thing.
好吧 碰巧格丽自己也曾经是新宠
Well, it happens Gerri was the new thing once.
记得吗
Remember?
你觉得他曾经睡过格丽吗
You think he ever boned Gerri?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只是觉得我们需要小心点
I just think we need to be careful.
怎么了
Aw, what's wrong?
你们都被折磨变形了 因为瑞亚站在你们的背上
You all wedgied up because Rhea stood on your back
像椭圆机一样把你们的双臂扭弯了吗
and worked your arms like an elliptical?
我只是在说 我在想 我们是不是应该有一个计划
I'm just saying, I wonder if we should have a plan,
你懂的 以防爸作出鲁莽的决定
you know, in case Dad does something rash.
康纳 我们准备好了
Connor, we're ready for you.
好的 祝我好运
Okay. Wish me luck.
嘿 老爸 是我 康纳·罗伊 你的儿子
Hey, Dad. It's me, Connor Roy, your son.
我只想说 你一直是我的超级英雄 老爸
I just want to say that you've always been my superhero, Dad.
你和坏人作斗争 而且你总是赢
You fight the bad guys and you always win.
我知道我们并没有
I know we don't get to spend
尽可能多地单独待一起 尽管我们很想这样
as much time together one-on-one as we'd like,
而这让我很难过
and that makes me sad,
但是作为你的儿子 我感到无比自豪
but I'm unbelievably proud to be your son.
我超级爱你 超级老爸
I super love you, Super-Dad.
嘿 怎么样
Hey, what's up?
嘿 你怎么样 声音很大的家伙
Hey, how are you? Loud!
-什么  -你穿的衣服和昨天一样
-What? -And you're wearing the same clothes as yesterday.
你希望我们认为你昨晚上床了
You want us to think you got laid.
想得美
Nice try.
-嘿 肯  -嘿
-Hey, Ken. -Hey.
西沃恩计划干掉瑞亚
Siobhan's planning to kill Rhea.
...不 我没有
...No. I'm not.
我们正在讨论 没有计划
We're having a discussion. There's no plan.
我只是在鼓励大家评估我们的选项
I'm just encouraging us to assess our options.
好的 那关我们事吗
Okay. Is that our business?
公司名字上面有我们名字 你说关我们事吗
The business with our name on it, is it our business?
我不知道 如果 你知道的 如果爸迷进去了...
I don't know. If-- You know, if Dad's into it...
通常来说 他的想法都是对的
Like, whatever he thinks is usually pretty on target.
好吧 我认为瑞亚很危险
Okay, well, I think Rhea is dangerous,
而且我认为我们必须阻止她
and I think we need to stop her.
好吧 很明显 是你需要阻止她
Well, it-- it's clear you need to stop her.
如果她拆分公司出售怎么办
What if she sells the company for parts?
八周前
Eight weeks ago,
爸准备卖掉整个集团
Dad was ready to kick over the whole sandcastle--
不过他没有这么做 不是吗
He didn't though, did he?
而是达成了一笔小交易 小西
Struck a little deal on the side instead, Shiv.
好吧 你知道吗 我们需要抛开个人恩怨 来一次家庭休战
All right. You know what? We need to put feelings aside and call a family truce,
因为我们要以每小时一千英里的时速
because we need to fuck her from 100 different directions
从100个不同方向操她 我说真的
at a thousand miles an hour. I'm serious.
...肯德尔
...Kendall.
嗯 我是说 我觉得...
Yeah, I mean, I guess...
最好把这话题保留在家庭内部
it would be nice to keep it in the family.
肯 也许讲讲那个感人的故事
Ken. Maybe tell that heartwarming story
就是你打算怎么杀死他然后接管公司的故事
about how you tried to kill him and take over the company.
那样应该会让那个老色鬼感动流泪
That ought to moisten the old peepers.
那 康纳 我 嗯...
So, Connor, I, um--
你知道沙漠里的沙子吗
Do you know the sand that's in Sands?
你的意思是 他们以5.29元一袋的价格卖给我的
You mean the nine metric tons of Gypsum white
那九公吨石膏白吗
they gouged me for 5.29 a bag?
我当然知道沙子
Sure, I know the sand.
那 我当时坐得离舞台非常近
So, I was sitting pretty close to the stage,
所以 我 我的位置很好
and so, I-- I had great seats,
然后 嗯 我觉得沙子里面可能住着什么东西
and, um-- and I think there's something maybe living in it,
也许 也许有什么东西在沙子里蓬勃发展
like per-- perhaps thriving in the sand,
比如沙螨 有可能吗
like sand mites, maybe?
我对此一无所知 也不承担任何法律责任
I know nothing about that and bear no legal responsibility.
你得和沙子供应商谈谈
You'll have to talk to the sand supplier,
和其他人一样
like everyone else.
是的 好的 好的 嗯...
Yeah, that's cool, that's cool, um...
飞三千英里这么远 就为了去装模作样
Three thousand miles to pose with signage.
幸亏他妈的我不忙
Thank fuck I'm not busy.
你现在还可以取消
You could still cancel.
不不不 瑞亚在这方面很聪明
No, no, no. Rhea's smart on this.
吃点晚餐 宣传下50年的经验 50年的成长
A little dinner, push 50 years experience, 50 years growth.
强调经验 历史
Stress the experience. History.
这是一个发布战略公告的平台
A platform on which to make a strategic announcement.
洛根
Logan.
在我们安顿下来之前
Before we settle in,
嗯 我们有一件小事想让你知道
um, there's a small matter we wanted to make you aware of.
曾在游轮公司担任会计的詹姆斯·韦塞尔
A former cruise employee, James Weissel in accounting,
他很清楚各种付款内幕
so quite inside the payments and so on,
好像被官司吓到了
seems to have gotten spooked by a lawsuit,
看上去他有可能要开口了
and seems like he might be about to talk.
我还以为我们把这一切都解决了呢
I thought we had this all sewn up.
-我说的是希望如此...  -不要...打断我
- I said I hoped-- - Don't... interrupt me.
你告诉我 这一切都解决了
You told me this was all sewn up.
为什么我现在才知道这件事
Why am I only hearing about this now?
他经历过90年代加勒比海的那些事
He was across the Caribbean '90s situation,
付款和其他所有操作
the payouts and all the other operations.
然后他另择高就了
And then he went up the ladder.
他知道影子日志的事情
He knows about the shadow logs.
他给老莫擦过很多屁股
He supervised a number of "Mo aftermaths."
好的 好的 给他点严重警告
Okay. Okay. Give him the storm warning.
让"狗日的密探"山姆去和他聊聊
Get rat-fucker Sam to give him the talk,
"我们拥有无穷的资源 我们会摧毁你的生活"
"We have endless resources. We will destroy your life."
-都有谁知道  -肯德尔 卡尔
-Who knows? -Kendall, Karl.
-瑞亚呢  -不 不知道
-Rhea? -No. Nope.
好
Good.
我真的不希望听到这些屁事 你知道吗
I really don't want this shit in my ears, you know?
想办法搞定
Figure it out.
那 真的是瑞亚在掌管
So, Rhea really took the reins
这个周末的计划吗
on this weekend planning?
是啊 她表现得很活跃
Yeah. She's been very active.
好吧...但是对你来说 一定很艰难
Well... Must be tough for you, though.
怎么会
How so?
我只是...
I just...
我知道他有了新的热情时会怎么样
I know how he can be when he has a new enthusiasm.
不用担心我
Don't worry about me.
我不是小孩子了
I'm not a child.
我不会每次打雷都吓得尿裤子的
I don't piss on the carpet every time it thunders.
我只是觉得我们有一些共同的利益
I just think we share some similar interests.
我的意思是 让她做这么多计划可以吗
I mean, is it okay to let her do this much planning?
如果她想给他开个惊喜派对
If she wants to throw him a big surprise party,
我有什么资格去破坏
who am I to spoil it?
舞台
The bandstand.
那里在搞什么 爸
What happened there, Pa?
...不同的东西
...different things.
是的 很多...是的 嘿
Yeah, a lot of...Yeah. Hey.
你和尤恩当时能去加拿大真是太幸运了
You and Ewan were lucky to make it out to Canada.
这里也不是什么人间地狱
Wasn't such a fucking hootenanny there either.
不 这个地方...
Nah. This place...
我环顾四周...我不知道
I look around and... I don't know.
我们回来过 嗯...我母亲去世的时候
We came back for, um... when my mother died,
但是一切都如此……复杂
but it was all so... complicated.
你无法解释
You can't explain it.
这不是你的想法
It's not what you think.
你看着旧照片
You look at the old pictures
他们希望你认为 这一切都他妈的那么简单
and they want you to think it's all so fucking simple,
但是那是...那是...
but it was... well, it was...
是的 嗯 我不知道那是什么
It was, um-- I don't know what it was.
那是...
It was, um...
那...不是他们说的那样 你知道吗
It wasn't... what they say, you know?
那就给我们讲个故事吧
Tell us a story, though.
-故事  -是的 以前那时候的故事
-Story? -Yeah, from back in the day.
是吗
Yeah?
你想知道以前的那些陈年往事吗
What, you want a bit about, old fucking Rosebud?
陈年往事就是穷得叮当响
Rosebud is a dollar bill.
所以不管付出什么代价 我都要离开这里
It's whatever it took to get me the fuck out of here.
故事不错 爸
Good story, Dad.
夫人
Madam.
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy.
很高兴欢迎你回家
A pleasure to welcome you home.
我可不记得我离开的时候有人伤心流泪过
I don't recall people shedding a tear when I left,
-不过 还是谢谢你  -谢谢你 先生
-but thank you. -Thank you, sir.
你好
Hello.
-你好 瑞亚  -雨果
-Hello, Rhea. -Hugo.
谢谢你的组织
Thank you for organizing this.
我的荣幸
My pleasure.
所以 你是那种玩弄了别人之后
So, are you a person who, can't look
就没胆量和别人眼睛对视的人吗
someone in the eye after you've fucked them?
我是诚心诚意的
I acted in good faith.
是啊
Yeah.
是的 我的意思是 这真的很可怕
Yeah, I mean, that's what's truly scary,
因为我认为 你还真的相信这一点
'cause I think you believe that.
怎么 你在外包你坑人的手段吗
What, do you outsource your fuckery?
你用右脑来进行励志演讲
You got the right brain for your TED Talks,
-然后用左脑杀人吗  -这样说很不公平
-left brain for your killings? -That's very unfair.
好吧 我现在很难过
Well, I feel bad now.
我把你推荐给了皮尔斯 然后事情失控了
I put you forward to Pierce, and it got out of hand.
你爸爸显然感觉自己被蒙在鼓里
Your dad obviously felt out of the loop
这又不是我故意的
and it wasn't as I intended.
是的 我听说你在草拟一个名单
Yeah, I hear you're putting some names together
-作为爸爸的总裁候选人  -各种人才
- for Dad's CEO search. -Various individuals.
包括你自己吗
Including yourself?
好吧 适合这种职位的人选本来就很有限
Well, the pool is small for this type of position.
是啊 哇 真是惊喜
Yeah. Wow. What a surprise.
他需要
He needs someone
在股东大会之前选定一个人 你知道这事的
before the shareholder meeting. You know that.
是的 我想知道你在向谁倾斜
Yeah, and I wonder which way you're leaning.
谁在你的推荐名单里
Who's catching your eye to recommend?
你是倾向于某人 比如说
You leaning towards someone, say, like me
现在很想杀了你的我
who wants to kill you,
还是说...倾向于你自己
or... yourself,
这样你就又有机会得到百万年薪了
for a second chance at a multi-million-dollar payday?
我很好奇 记得告诉我最新消息哦
I'm intrigued. Keep me posted.
那 你有没有听到什么
So, are you hearing anything majorly major
关于某个大事或者别的事的重大消息
about big shit or whatever through the shit-vine?
哪方面
In what sense?
金发小妖精那方面
In the sense of the little blonde goblin.
她打算攫取所有的力量吗
Is she about to gobble up all the power?
听着 弗兰克很担心
So, um, Frank is concerned.
他说 这次感觉不太一样
He says this feels like something new.
是的 但是爸就是这样的人 对不对
Yeah, but he does this, right?
爸 我的意思是 还记得他给那个小妞买竖琴的事吗
Dad. I mean, remember when he bought that chick a harp?
莎莉·安妮吗
Sally Anne?
她甚至都不知道怎么弹奏
She didn't even know how to play it.
这次情况不一样
This is something else.
他正在失去焦点
He's losing focus.
一周有四个晚上出去吃晚餐
Out to dinner four nights a week.
股东投票迫在眉睫
The shareholder vote is going to be close.
如果董事会被换了 那将是一次大清洗
If the board gets replaced, it'll be a clean sweep.
我们可以安排一些备选成员
We could do with options.
我已经确保爱德华进入名单了
I've made sure that Eduard is invited.
你能利诱他吗
Could you seduce?
...我不知道
...I don't know.
你觉得我很诱人吗
Do you find me seductive?
我可以给他提出条件
I can give him a rim.
-我可以提出很好的条件  -他们可以把我们私有化吗
-I could rim with vim. -Could they take us private?
他们想让我们开设一个宣传新闻节目
They want us to open up a propaganda news operation.
就是这样 罗曼
It's that serious, Roman.
我们得到钱了 一切搞定 而监督少得多
We get the money, boom. Much less oversight.
好的 好吧 我会...
Okay. Well, I will...
那我再和他谈谈
I will talk to him, then.
对了 还有一件事情 很快
And, um, one more thing, real quick.
我们应该...结婚吗
Should we... get married?
什么
What?
你知道的 不是那种结婚 类似那样的
You know, not that. Like, an equivalent.
...类似的事情 比如 我绑架你 强迫你和我同住
...A thing, like I abduct you and force you to live with me.
...一点也不类似
...That's not equivalent.
那么 你杀了我
Well, then, you kill me,
你切掉我的鸡巴 你懂的 切掉某个身体部位
you chop my dick off, you know, something.
我在开玩笑呢 不过 你懂我的意思的
I'm kidding but you know what I'm saying.
...你吃我 我吃你 就像他们在德国做的那样
...You eat me, I eat you, like they do in Germany.
总之 有很多需要考虑的 我明白 所以 让它...
Anyway, lot to think about, I get it. So, let it...
再见
Bye.
-嘿  -嘿 那
-Hey. -Hey, so,
还没有消退 对吧
it hasn't worn off, right?
简直是一次翻天覆地世纪大性爱
Like, that was a century-defining fuck.
-你哪位啊  -詹妮弗 詹妮弗
-Who is this again? -Jennifer, Jennifer.
好了 那么 我们要干嘛
All right. So, what are we going to do here?
我觉得我们应该买一个岛
I feel like we should maybe buy an island,
放一张巨大的岛那么大的床 然后整天操来操去
put in a giant island sized bed, and just make love all day.
你去过敦提吗 你想来敦提吗
You ever been to Dundee? You wanna come to Dundee?
那我的戏剧怎么办
What about my play?
戏剧...
The play?...
我的意思是 也就翘班两个晚上 来吧
I mean, it's, like, two nights off. Come on.
又不是亚瑟·米勒的剧 对吧
It's not Arthur Miller, right?
而且 我有一家电影制片厂呢
And, I kinda own a movie studio.
嗯...敦提在哪里
Um... Where is Dundee?
不如你在去机场的路上
How about you look it up on your phone
在手机上查一下 因为我现在安排个司机过来
on the way to the airfield, because I'm sending you a driver
今晚我安排一架喷气飞机把你送过来
and I'm getting you a jet ride over here tonight.
以前的自来水味道很好
The tap water used to taste sensational.
味道已经变了
It's changed. .
罗伊先生 你有空吗
Mr. Roy. You have a second?
-当然  -街上的交通...
-Sure. -Transportation to the streets...
玛西娅 你看起来真美
Marcia, you look lovely.
谢谢
Thank you.
...那...
...So...
我有件事想问你
I have something I wanted to ask you.
你有没有定期接受性传播疾病的检查
Are you regularly tested for sexually transmitted diseases?
什么意思
Excuse me?
他和我仍然睡在一起
He and I still sleep together.
我不知道他是怎么告诉你的
I don't know what he tells you.
对不起 我...我不知道你在说什么
I'm sorry, I-- I don't know what you're talking about.
知道你很干净 我才能更放心
So, I will be more relaxed to know that you are clean.
我又不知道你还在和谁睡觉
I don't know who else you're screwing.
这 这个话题不适合...谈论...
This-- This isn't appropriate to-- to talk of--
-就像...  -听着
-of-- of-- Like... -Listen..
我为此战斗过 我输过 也赢过
I have fought and I have lost, and I have fought and won,
但是如果我输了
but when I lose,
我的对手通常会失去眼睛或者灵魂
the other one will generally lose an eye or a soul.
嘿 对不起
Hey, sorry.
抱歉 玛西娅
Sorry, Marcia,
可以在酒会之前给我们五分钟时间吗
could you give us five, just before drinks?
当然 谢谢你 瑞亚
Of course. Thank you, Rhea.
一切都好吗
Everything okay?
最新情况是什么
What's the latest?
当然 一切都好 离目标很近了
Sure. All good. Honing in.
好 好
Good. Good.
我的意思是 谢谢你张罗这个小晚宴
I mean, thank you for taking the lead on the little dinner,
邀请那些政客 你知道的 其他等等
all the politics and, you know, what-not.
好吧 我很乐意帮忙 但是我感觉到一些骚乱
Well, I'm pleased to help, but I'm sensing some turbulence.
小西
Shiv.
小西 她喜怒无常
Shiv. She runs hot.
她把自己
She makes boogie men
丢在卧室地板上的衣服当成了夜魔
out of the clothes she dumps on her bedroom floor.
一直都这样
Always has.
好吧 只要你不介意一点点反馈
Well, just as long as you don't mind a bit of feedback.
她有点生气 气势汹汹的样子
A few noses are out of joint. Strong French feelings.
我担心我可能会被法棍弄瞎
I'm worried I might get blinded with a baguette.
就说瑞亚殴打她的狗或者男友 我也不知道
Just say Rhea beats her dog or boyfriend or I don't know.
...爸爸会喜欢的
...Dad would love that.
你认为的弹药并不是真的弹药
The thing you think is ammo is not ammo.
我们需要明确 直接 有路线的攻击
We need to be clear, direct, with a line of attack.
你知道"自由 两面派"
You know, "liberal, duplicitous."
"她是一片双面雪花 衣服上有精液"
"She's a two-faced snowflake with cum on her dress."
告诉她去问问罗丝的事
Tell her to ask about Rose.
-我操  -是的
-Shit. -Yup!
这听起来很有计划 芬芳的阻扰
This sounds schemey. Redolent of thwart.
是啊 你觉得在瑞亚旁边施展点魅力怎么样
Yeah. How do you feel about oozing a bit near Rhea?
只是 你知道 有点...
Just, you know, sorta...
有点什么
Sorta what?
好吧 你知道 引起...引起她傻笑
Well, you know, get-- get a bit giggly.
继续努力 但是 这样我爸才可以看到
Work it. But so that my dad can see.
我的意思是 这样并不会干掉她 但是一切都会有帮助
I mean, it doesn't kill her, but everything helps.
我有一个想法 也许瑞亚可以在祝酒词里提一下
I have this idea that maybe Rhea can mention in a toast.
扔个小手榴弹吗
Lob a little grenade?
你是在帮我拉皮条吗
Are you pimping me out?
不 不 不用做什么疯狂的事 汤姆
No, no. Nothing crazy, Tom.
只是让她笑 稍微动动手臂
Just make her laugh. Work the arms a bit.
来一点手臂性爱
Have a bit of elbow sex.
你说的是我可怕的老板痴迷的那个女人吗
The woman who my terrifying boss is obsessed with?
你要我和她调情吗
You want me to flirt with her?
汤姆 拜托 不是...
Tom, come on. Not--
不是那种肮脏的调情 而是有害的调情
Not dirty flirty. Just hurty flirty.
肯德尔 你准备好忽悠瑞亚了吗
Kendall, you ready to wind up Rhea?
-你被她玩了吗  -是啊
-Did you fuck with her? -Yeah.
我们试试用罗丝来玩弄她
Let's try Rose out on her.
看看她的耳朵会不会被夹
See if she gets a clip on the ears.
-嘿 这个活动太好了 这很棒  -是的 嗯...
-Hey, this is great. It's great. -Yeah, um...
是的...你...
Yeah... Do you--
你觉得我说点祝酒词可以吗
Do you think it would be okay if I made a little toast?
我的意思是 我不想惹恼任何人
I mean, I don't want to piss anybody off.
是的 绝对可以
Yeah, absolutely.
你可以 嗯...
You could, um...
你可以向他的母亲海伦致敬
You could toast his mother, Helen.
-对  -还有...
-Right. -And...
我不知道 也许提一提罗丝
I don't know, maybe mention Rose,
他姐姐罗丝 她已经不在人世了
his sister Rose who is no longer with us.
他可能会喜欢的
He might appreciate that.
-谢谢  -是的 应该的
-Thank you. -Yeah, sure.
晚上好 各位
Evening, one and all.
我知道我是干果组合的新成员
I know I'm the new nut in the trail mix,
但是...
but, um...
我只是想感谢大家的参与 一起来...
I just wanted to thank you all for joining, and to...
祝贺我们这位毫不留情的揭匾者
congratulate our implacable plaque unveiler.
而且 鉴于明天的荣誉...
And, given tomorrow's honor...
让我们一起举杯 向那些...
let's raise our glasses to those...
今晚无法和我们在一起的人致敬
who are with us tonight in absentia.
-敬洛根的母亲海伦  -敬海伦
-Logan's mother Helen. -To Helen.
还有他的姐姐罗丝
And his sister Rose.
那...干杯 各位
So... cheers, everyone.
-干杯  -干杯
-Cheers. -Slàinte mhath.
这午餐不错
This is some lunch.
每个人都被每件事情冒犯了
Everybody's offended by everything.
哇 干得漂亮 看看你 融合得很好
Wow. Well done. Look at you, fitting right in,
就像我十二岁时跟在我屁股后面的营地辅导员一样
like a camp counselor in my butt when I was 12.
那是济慈吗
Is that Keats?
匿名的
Anonymous.
我看到你做的事了
I see your thing.
很好 有用
It's good. It works.
你像是一个劲头十足的有趣枪手 只不过已经徐娘半老
You're kinda like a peppy, fun-gun set to "MILF,"
像...
with like, a...
进一步说 你就是那些傻逼用起来
Lean In,  woman-y branding thing that works well
效果还不错的女性品牌产品
with the Fitbit-moron-whatever people.
美中不足的是 我是一只花蝴蝶
I'm a sort of butterfly in the ointment:
色彩缤纷但令人毛骨悚然
colorful but wriggly.
我可以看到我们的合作
I could see us collaborating.
是吗 是的 你可以看到吗
Yeah? Yeah, you can see that?
是的 拍老笨蛋的马屁
Yeah, buttering up the old dunce?
-干得不错 滚开  -不
-Nice work. Fuck off. -No.
我知道你的名声
I get your rep. .
有些标签需要一段时间才能撕掉
Some labels take a while to peel off,
但是 我碰巧认为 你是他们所有人中间
but I happen to think you have the best instincts
直觉最好的
of all of them.
瞎扯 不过 谢谢
Well, bullshit, but thank you.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿 这里才是派对的地方 看看我们
Hey, this is where the party's at. Look at us,
所有最酷最美的人都汇聚在一个地方
all the cool and the beautiful people in one spot.
这里就像VIP区一样
This is like the VIP area, right here.
对吧 这里应该围一圈警戒线
Right? It should be, like, cordoned off
用那种丝绒绳 搞一点VIP小圈子的氛围
with, a-- like, a velvet rope, a bit of VIP bondage.
我的天啊
My goodness.
嗨 爸 听着
Hey, Pa, so, listen.
-...剧本...  -对不起 我们...
- ... The play-- -Yeah, I'm sorry that we--
-我们没有来 嗯...  -不用担心
-we didn't, um... -No worries.
不是说这个 我只想说 剧本花了一大笔钱...
No, it's just costing a pretty penny and...
开始出现一些财务上的担忧
a few financial worries starting to bubble.
-很高兴和你聊聊  -嗯 别担心 儿子
-Be good to chat. -Yeah, don't worry, son.
我相信你会解决的
I'm sure you'll work it out.
...所以...所以 瑞亚 你的...你的家在哪里
...So... So, Rhea, where's-- where's home for you?
四海为家
Home was all over.
我好像听说过你的母亲...这是不是真的
And did I hear that your mother-- Is this true,
她是民主社会主义者的志愿者吗
she volunteers for the Democratic Socialists?
我的天 老天啊 伙计们 当心
My! God, folks, watch out,
我们的大酒杯里有个圣母婊
we've got a libtard in the punch bowl.
快点 把你的工资单藏起来 免得她拿到更多联邦政府的钱
Quick, hide your pay stubs before she takes more federal.
…是啊 我们也不是每件事都意见一致
...Yeah, we don't see eye to eye on everything.
对
Right.
对不起 不用给她倒了 她不喝酒
I'm sorry, none for her. She doesn't drink.
嗯...
Um...
好吧 我 喝一点点
Well, I, sip.
但是...但是...不 不 不怎么喝
But-- But-- N-- No, not really, no.
嗯 对不起 嗯...
Yeah. Sorry, I...
嗯 没什么...
Well, not a great deal. Um...
我很确定 和大家的酒量相比
I'm pretty sure, maybe just a drop
也许只能算一滴酒 对敬酒来说的话
if you can fit it in there. For a toast.
丁 丁 丁 丁 丁 丁 丁 丁
Ding. Ding. Ding. Ding. Ding. Ding. Ding. Ding.
-好吧 我这是敬酒  -太好了
-Well, here's a toast. -Great.
我只是想说 这一切很棒
I guess I just wanna say how great it is
我们认识和爱的每一个人都聚集在一个地方
to have everyone we know and love in one place
庆祝我们父亲的一生
to celebrate our dad's life.
-是啊 说得好  -说得好
-Yeah. Hear, hear. -Hear, hear.
向瑞亚大喊一声 感谢她策划了一场精彩的葬礼
Shout out to Rhea for planning a wonderful funeral.
我的意思是……纪念
I mean...memorial.
不 夜晚
No, evening.
别这样...
Please...
这是我的荣幸 向一个毫无疑问...
It's my honor to salute a man...
有一天会埋葬我们所有人的男人致敬
who will one day bury us all, no doubt.
-说得好  -开心的日子
-Hear, hear. -Happy days.
-说得好 干杯  -干杯
-Hear, hear. Cheers. -Cheers.
干杯 爸爸
Cheerio, Dad.
向爸爸致敬
To Dad.
我背上有一个疮
I have one in my backside.
千万不要挠它
Just don't scratch it.
天啦 我觉得跟一个抗议者在一起的感觉更奇怪
God. I feel like it's weirder with one protester.
就像 你不知道是该和他进行眼神交流 还是...
Like, you don't know whether to make eye contact, or...
好吧 他确实在那方面做得很好
Well, he really went with the first draft on that one.
尽管如此 公平地说 这抗议非常有效
Still, to be fair, it's pretty effective.
显然 这里没有那么令人反感
Apparently, it's less offensive over here.
这就像称呼某人为好友
It's like calling someone a buddy.
看看这个烂地方 你在跟我开玩笑吗
Look at this shit. Are you kidding me?
如果这个房子在布鲁克林 很容易卖500万
If this place was in Brooklyn, it'd be worth five mil, easy.
这个也还好
This is, like, fine.
完全可以
It's totally fine.
我愿意住这里
I'd live here.
我的意思是 我不会住这里 但是有人会
I mean, I wouldn't but someone could.
我的意思是 你告诉我 他住在露天下水道
I mean, you told me he lived in an open sewer
是被老鼠抚养长大的 但是这里...
and was raised by rats but this is...
是的 你应该去那个窗口偷看
Yeah, you should go peek in that window.
那里肯定是一间浴室
That's for sure a bathroom.
这个烂房子是战前修的
And this fucker is pre-war.
爸爸不可能在桶里拉屎
There's no way Dad shat in a bucket.
这个东西让情况变得更糟了
This stuff's making it worse.
我觉得这个东西在吸引蠓虫
And I feel like this stuff is attracting midges.
我的沙螨被蠓虫咬了
My sand mites are getting bitten by midges.
你住口吧
Just stop.
-我现在皮肤很不舒服  -赶紧住口
-I'm just uncomfortable in my skin right now. -Just stop.
开始了
Here we go.
房子变化很大吗
Has it changed much?
是的...全变了
Yeah... Everything.
他在干嘛
What's he doing?
好吧 房子就在那
Okay. There it is.
我应该做些什么
What am I supposed to do?
我想也许拍张照片 他们说你可以进去
I think maybe a photo. They've said you can go in.
不了 谢谢
No. Thank you.
我们走吧
Let's go.
-等等  -他妈的什么鬼啊
-Wait. Wait. -What the fuck?
回忆
Memories.
...听着 我有个最新情况
...So, I have an update.
是吗
Yeah?
詹姆斯·韦塞尔 我们真的不想打扰你爸
James Weissel. We don't really want to bother your dad.
我们知道他在享受这一刻
We know he's enjoying this.
有一个决定 我们希望你来拿主意
There's a call, and we might like your input.
-可以吗  -嗯
-That okay? -Yeah.
是这样的 我们向韦斯莱曼先生发出了威胁 也给了报价
So, we made the threat/offer to Mr. Weaselman.
五百万提高到了一千万
Five rising to ten.
但他拒绝了
But he said no.
他拒绝了一千万 他为什么会拒绝一千万
He said no to ten? Why would he say no to ten mil?
我不知道 扮强硬好抬价吗
I don't know, playing hardball?
我们需要处理掉这个麻烦
We need this to go away,
-所以我会把价格加倍  -嗯
-so I'm gonna double the offer. -Yeah.
不惜一切让他心动 对吧
Anything to get him to roll, right?
嗯 没错 听起来很聪明
Yeah, right. Sounds smart.
好的 所以 我只是想让你知道
Okay. So, I just wanted to let you know.
很高兴让你爸爸保持愉快的心情
Nice to keep your dad in a good mood
去参加庆祝活动
for the festivities.
当然
Absolutely.
罗伊先生 很高兴你能来
Mr. Roy. So happy you could make it.
好吧 我们来看看我的钱都买了些什么 好吗
Well, let's see what my money bought, shall we?
这里的一切都是最先进的
Everything's state of the art.
着墨 卷筒纸胶印机
Inking, web-offset press.
我们喜欢说
We like to say,
我们的配置比大多数英国报纸都要好
we've got a better set up than most UK papers.
哇
Wow.
一整所学校 学习如何在标题党新闻聚合器上实习
A whole school for how to intern at a clickbait aggregator?
是啊
Yeah.
"你永远都不会得到报酬的十个理由"
"Ten reasons why you're never getting paid."
对不起 我不得不问
I'm sorry, I have to ask.
你为什么要玩弄我
Why are you trying to fuck me?
玩弄你 你什么意思
Trying to fuck you? What do you mean?
罗丝 我们俩都知道那是什么意思
Rose. We both know what that was.
如果有的话 我只是
If anything, I'm just,
代表我妹妹 弗兰克和格丽进行了一点小小的冒犯
mildly offended on behalf of my sister and Frank, Gerri.
我想知道媒体的反应 但是
And I wonder about the optics, but,
嘿 我爸知道 所以...
hey, my dad knows, so...
尽管这样
Even so.
坦白说 我不知道你是怎么做到的
I don't know how you've done it, frankly.
你所经历的那一切
What with everything you've been through.
不过你很好
You're good, though.
对
Right.
-谢谢  -不
-Thank you. -No.
你真的很厉害
You're good,
但你现在还在磨砺之中
but you're still in the rock tumbler right now.
你还没准备好
You're not ready.
我很好
I'm good.
我的意思是 我已经抛开过去了
I mean, I'm over my shit.
我遇到了一个新朋友
And I've met someone new.
我的意思是 她非常棒
I mean, she is fantastic.
所以 是的 我...
And, so, yeah, I'm--
我并没有处在你认为的那种情况中
I'm not in the place you think I'm in.
不 没关系
No, it's okay.
但是 等到这一切水落石出明朗之时...
But when we're out on the other side of this all...
是你
it's you.
我现在告诉你 一直都是你
I'm telling you now. It's always been you.
好的...
Well...
谢谢
thank you.
我不知道这个情况 但是谢谢
I don't know about that, but thank you.
嗯...他们在问 你要不要留下来吃午餐
Um... They're asking if you want to stay for lunch.
去他妈的 不吃
Fuck, no.
我会确保把信息反馈给他们的 "去他妈的 不吃" 收到
I'll be sure to feed that back to them. "Fuck, no." Got it.
看看是谁来了
Look who made it.
机场的名字你也要改吗
Are you going to change the name of the airport, too?
等你飞走的时候
As you fly off?
玛西娅打给你的吗
Marcia call you?
不是 是你的新宠
No. Your new one.
好吧
Right.
洛根罗伊新闻学院
The Logan Roy School of Journalism.
下一步是什么
What's next?
开膛手杰克妇女健康诊所吗
The Jack the Ripper Women's Health Clinic?
你在镇上逛过了吗
You, had a poke around the town?
我已经看够了
I've seen enough.
你把你的名字像涂鸦一样
You've been spreading your name all over this place
在这个地方乱写乱画
like it was graffiti.
他们试图让我进那套老房子
They tried to get me to go into the old house.
再做块牌匾吗
Another plaque.
我在音乐台那里看到了一只槲鸫
I saw a mistle thrush at the bandstand.
你当然看到了
Sure, you did.
这个老混蛋
This old bastard.
我以前经常把我看到的鸟记录下来
I used to keep a log of the birds I'd see.
你爷爷会检查我的记录
Your grandpa would go through it
然后擦掉他不相信我见过的那些鸟
and scrub out the ones he didn't believe I'd seen.
你总是对你的所见所闻夸大其词
You were always fairly generous with your sightings.
-喂  -您好 尊敬的股东
-Yeah. -Hello, valued shareholder,
-很快 您将做出一个至关重要的决定...  -这他妈什么鬼
you will soon have a critical decision to make... -What the fuck is this?
...与您在韦斯达的投资有关
...regarding your investment in Waystar.
他们他妈的用机器人给我打电话
They're fucking robocalling me now.
我想说 很高兴见到
I was gonna say, it's nice to see you and,
你和你的老弟聊天
and the old brother having a chat.
是啊...
Yeah, well...
是的 他是个顽固的老家伙
Yeah, he's a tough old bird.
-但是...但是 他...  -他在道德上已经破产了
- But-- But he's-- he's-- -He's morally bankrupt.
他是个无足轻重的人 对于这个星球的死亡.​​..
He's a nothing man who may well be...
他很可能比其他任何一个人...
more personally responsible for the death of this planet...
都负有更大的个人责任
than any other single human being.
他还创立了卡利斯皮特朗特许经营权
He also makes the Kalispitron franchise,
你知道的 这是个可靠的大众娱乐活动
which is, you know, solid, mediocre entertainment.
就即将失去的生命而言
In terms of the lives that will be lost
他是在为否认气候变化的人卖淫
by his whoring for the climate change deniers,
有一个非常有说服力的论点...
there's a very persuasive argument to be made...
他比希特勒还要糟糕
that he's worse than Hitler.
好吧...
Right, well...
如果你停止为他工作 我将不胜感激
And I'd appreciate it if you'd stop working for him.
好吧 嗯...
Okay, um, well...
所以 我已经有了很大的进步
so, I have moved up significantly,
这听起来可能很愚蠢
and this might sound dumb,
但是 也许我可以打入他们内部 做一些工作
but maybe I can kind of work it from the inside,
-那样的话...  -如果你拒绝离职
-and that way-- -If you refuse,
我认为这完全在我的权限范围内...
I think it's well within my rights...
我会把你的名字从我的遗嘱受益人
to remove your name from amongst the beneficiaries
里面删除
of my last will and testament.
好的
Okay.
因为那...那是非常多的钱
Because that's-- that's quite a pretty penny.
大概2.5亿
Around 250 mil.
而且我相信 绿色和平组织会非常感激我的捐款的
And I'm sure Greenpeace would be very much obliged.
不 当然...那是一大笔钱
No, de-- definitely, that is quite a pickle.
这是个艰难的抉择啊
That is a tough one.
-老兄  -嘿 兄弟
- Dude. -Hey, brother.
天哪 你闻起来像棉花糖
My God, you smell like cotton candy.
我都想舔你的脖子了
I almost want to lick your neck.
谢谢你的光临 伙计
Thanks for coming, man.
我爸会非常高兴看到...
My dad'll be very pleased when he sees, you know,
老朋友和...
old friends and...
你好 先生 是的 我要一杯那种美酒
Hi, yes, sir. Yeah, I'll take one of those golden beauties.
这是什么比赛
What's this?
苏格兰足球 我正在考虑进去
Scottish. I'm thinking of getting in.
苏格兰足球吗
Scottish kicky-ball?
看上去就像两个太监抢着操一个信箱
It looks like two eunuchs trying to fuck a letterbox.
我喜欢希伯尼安队 或者 凯尔蒂赫斯队
I'm liking the look of Hibs. Or Hearts.
是吗
Yeah? .
赫斯队 那是我父亲的球队
Hearts, that's my dad's team.
他唯一能忍受的童年遗物
The only childhood relic he can stomach.
西班牙经纪人 大个子
Agent in Spain, big baller. .
我买下俱乐部 他借给我九个超级棒的球员
I buy the club, he loans me nine shit hot players.
我们节节攀升
We climb the ladder,
拿下第二个冠军联赛的位置
take the second Champion's League space,
在欧足联全力支持欧洲超级联赛
UEFA goes full European super-league,
翻盘 然后抽身
flip it, walk away.
我根本不懂你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about,
不过听起来很他妈的滑 老兄
but it sounds fucking slick, dude.
比海豚的背部还要滑
Slicker than cum on a dolphin's back.
你想加入吗
You want in?
也许
Maybe.
...但是 我们可以谈谈我们之前谈的事吗
...But can we talk about what we talked about?
你知道的 注入大笔投资 甚至是将我们私有化
You know, a major injection, or even taking us private.
你跟你爸谈过吗
Have you talked to your dad?
这事我们之间就可以谈
It's a conversation we can have.
那我们应该他妈的好好谈谈
Then we should totally have that fucking conversation,
就像两个他妈的可卡因拍卖师
like two fucking auctioneers on coke.
我可以100%地代表我父亲工作
I have total 360 latitude to work on my father's behalf.
酷 我也是 完全可以代表我爸
Cool. Same with me, with my dad, yeah.
操 我们这么相似 真是很奇怪
Fuck, it's weird how much we're the same.
好样的
Attaboy.
把它踢进网袋里 你这个疯狂踢球的混蛋
Sock it in the net sack, you crazy kick ball bastards.
和我一起买下他们
Buy them with me.
一人一半
Fifty-fifty.
买...他们...
Buy the-- them? The...
...嗯 我得想一想
...Yeah, let me have a think.
我的意思是 我没有看到什么不好的地方 除了...
I mean, I don't really see a downside, other than...
我对苏格兰足球毫不了解 毫无兴趣以外
zero knowledge or interest in Scottish football,
不过 好的 我想一想 赫斯队
but yeah, let me have a little think. Hearts.
你只是在看高尔夫球场的介绍吗
Are you just looking at golf courses?
比如色情高尔夫
Like golf porn.
我可以拿走浴室里的肥皂吗
Am I allowed to take those soaps in the bathroom?
是啊 管它妈的 都拿走好了
Yeah. Fuck it, take it all.
嗯
Yeah.
-嗨  -嘿 康纳
-Hi. -Hey, Connor.
-你在干嘛...  -我们正在做准备
- Whatcha doing? ... -We're just getting ready.
-好  -几点...几点开始
-Good. -What time's-- ...What time's the thing?
我想 八点才会是高潮
I don't think the big surprise is until eight.
-那...  -威拉要我了解一下
-So... -Willa asked me to check in,
因为詹妮弗是演员阵容的重要成员
'cause Jennifer is, like, a key member of the cast.
有没有可能
Would it be possible
让詹妮弗回到舞台上去
to send Jennifer back to be on stage?
好吧 恐怕不行
Well, no, I'm afraid,
因为我和詹妮弗目前正在进行
because Jennifer and I are currently engaged
史无前例的伟大的性爱探险
in one of the all-time great psychosexual expeditions.
我们就像正在做爱的刘易斯和克拉克
We're like the Lewis and Clarke of fucking.
拜托 老弟 我在这里求你了
Come on, man. I'm begging you here.
我...我正在流血 我承担不起这样
I-- I'm bleeding out. I can't afford this.
对不起 老兄 但是 娱乐圈就是这样
I'm sorry, dude, but, that's showbiz.
-我对这样的结果非常不满  -我 我知道 我很抱歉
-I am very unhappy with this outcome. -I-- I know. I'm sorry.
我不是想在瑞亚的庆祝活动中令人扫兴
Not wanting to put a dampener on Rhea's celebrations
或是别的什么 但是我们是时候干死她了
or anything, but it's time we killed her dead.
用块石头砸碎她的头骨
Smash her skull in with a rock.
-棒呆了  -好的
-Nice. -Okay.
减轻我们痛苦的方法 小妹
Way to ease us in, sis.
这次活动会不会有"小不点儿" 我很期待"小不点儿"[猫和老鼠中的贪吃小老鼠的角色]
Will there be nibbles at this event? I was expecting nibbles.
我想的是...我们有什么就直接告诉他
What I'm thinking is we just-- We tell him direct.
我们直接告诉他 我们所有人 我们不接受
We just tell him, all of us, we won't have it.
-我能发言吗  -好啊
-Should I maybe take the floor? -Okay.
瑞亚真的会成为世界上最糟糕的事情吗
Would Rhea really be the worst thing in the world?
还是说 一个外面的女人现在加入进来确实有意义
Or does a woman from outside actually make sense right now?
好吧 懂了 她 她搞定你了
Okay, right. Well, she-- she got to you.
没有 只是...
No. Just-- -
我在两条战线上战斗
I'm fighting on two fronts
我可能得向爸爸
and I might have to make a request to Dad
提一座桥的情况
about a bridge situation,
-而她对此一直很理解  -这是胡扯 肯 你说说
-and she's been understanding. -This is bullshit. Ken?
-嗯...  -嗯什么
-Well... -Well?
拜托
Come on.
她...你也支持她吗 篮板王
Sh-- You're backing her too, rebounder?
没有 我...我只是...
No, I-- I just...
我只是认为 或许... -你只是... 你就是支持她
I just think that maybe... -You just...? You are.
...你的手伸的太长了
...you've overplayed your hand.
不好意思 她是怎么搞定你的
Excuse me? How did she get to you?
你觉得自己会在某个时候得到另一次机会
You think you'll be given another shot at some point,
是这样吗 不会有了
ever? No.
-还有 罗曼 你也是吗 不会有的  -我是说...
- And, Roman, you? No. -Well, I mean...
不 她认为你是个混蛋
No, she thinks you're a dipshit,
也许你真的是太混蛋了 所以不自知
or maybe you're just too much of a fucking dipshit to see that.
去你妈的 我比你更懂这个行业
Fuck you. I know more about this business than you.
-实际上比你们任何人都懂  -罗曼 没人他妈的在乎
- More than any of you, actually. -Roman, no one gives a fuck
-管理培训  -爸爸在乎 格丽在乎
-about management training. -Dad does. Gerri does.
那就是公司的托儿所
It's corporate daycare.
这个反驳根本就不行
That's not a good retort!
-别他妈傻笑了  -小西
-Don't fucking laugh at that. -Shiv.
-谢谢你这么认真  -我是很认真
-Thanks for taking this seriously. -I do.
只是...这很显而易见
It's just... It's transparent.
...你知道 瑞亚是爸爸想找的人
...-You know, Rhea's who Dad wants.
显然 所以...
Clearly. So...
-但是他错了  -是的 但是...
-But he's wrong. -Yeah, but--
-以防万一你想要我的书面形式  -也许 你知道吗 你应该...
-In case you want it in writing. -Maybe, you know, you should just, like--
放弃
like, give it up.
我完全坦白 我开始喜欢她了
Full disclosure, I'm starting to like her.
他喜欢她
He likes her.
嗯 这就是不和康纳达成计划的原因
Yeah, this is why you don't hatch a plan with Connor,
总是第一个倒戈
the first fucking pancake.
第一个倒戈 好的 谢谢
First pancake. Okay, thank you.
你乳臭未干呢 你们知道吗 你们都没有经历过
You're a brat. You know, none of you have been through
我经历过的事 所以...
what I've been through, so just...
噢 我妈妈被送进了疯人院
Aw! My mommy got sent to the booby hatch
-现在我很难过  -滚开
-and now I'm sad. -Fuck off.
我觉得你在这件事情上太过情绪化了
I think you're being too emotional about this whole thing.
-我他妈的天哪  -我觉得他正在...
-My fucking God. -I think he's trying...
-你是在给我打情感牌吗  -...向你说教
-Are you doing the emotional card on me? -...to mansplain things to you.
-去他妈的  -我的意思是...
-Fuck's sake. -I mean...
我的意思是 我本来想向你说教的
I mean, I was gonna mansplain it to you,
但是我觉得 他做得很好
but I think he did a very good job.
罗曼 肯德尔和康纳
Roman, Kendall and Connor.
基本上 这是他妈的一场灾难
Basically, it was a fucking disaster.
-嗯 我很遗憾  -不 我们只需要...
-Well, I'm sorry. - No, we just need to...
让他知道 非常直接地告诉他
let him know, be very direct:
她想把手伸进你的裤子里
she tried to put her hands down your pants.
不
No!
你说真的吗 通常不会这样说吧
Seriously? That's not a normal thing to ask?
并不是说她真的打算...我不知道
Not actually say that she tried to-- I don't know.
我的意思是 也许还有一个世界
And I mean because also, maybe, there is a world
瑞亚...
in which Rhea...
更有意义...在我看来
makes more sense... for me
就是...就是这样 也许吧
is the-- is the truth. Maybe.
拜托 一个你几乎不认识的女人
Excuse me? The woman who you barely know
对你来说 比你老婆更有意义吗
makes more sense to you than your wife?
好了 这很复杂
Come on, it's complicated.
你爸爸很复杂
Your dad is complicated.
你觉得你干掉瑞亚
You think if you kill Rhea,
他就会自动把接班人位置还给你吗
he's just gonna give it back to you automatically?
不会的
No.
好吧 汤姆 我不会放弃的
Okay, well, Tom, I won't give up.
我不会
I won't.
他给了我一个他妈的提议
He made me a fucking offer,
现在我要兑换这个优惠券
and I'm gonna redeem that coupon.
那 出席的有 市长
So, we got, the Lord Provost,
商会会长 议会领导...
the Chamber of Commerce, Leader of the Council...
多少 20到30个人吗
What? 20 to 30 faces?
-我说得对吗  -我不知道
-Is that right? -I don't know.
我又不是你的秘书
Je suis pas ta secretaire.
...听着 你想待多久就待多久
...Look, you stay as long as you like,
我喝完汤就溜 说我要接电话
I'm gonna bolt after the soup, say I have calls.
我他妈的只想离开这里
I just wanna get the fuck out.
好的
Okay.
宴请国王
Feting the king.
让我想起了塔西佗
Tacitus comes to mind.
是啊 塔西佗 经典的塔西佗
Yeah, yeah. Tacitus. Classic Tacitus.
他造就了一片荒地 然后称之为帝国
He's made a wasteland and calls it an empire.
天啦 塔西佗...他只是...只是...
God, Tacitus... He just-- just--
他的身边都是杀手 没有抚育之手
All killer, no filler with him.
他有说过什么不好的名言吗
Did he ever have a bad quote?
你递交辞职报告了吗
Have you tendered your resignation?
我这榆木脑袋还在考虑这个问题
Just working that out in the old noggin still.
哇
Whoa.
显然...
Apparently...
我们可能正在受到坏嗡嗡声的困扰
we may be suffering from bad buzz.
不管我们有什么好的嗡嗡声
Whatever good buzz we had
都已经被无处不在的坏嗡嗡声给消解了
has been wiped out by pervasive bad buzz.
好了 新闻 聚过来
Okay, news. Huddle.
好了 各位 开始了 开始了
Okay, everyone. Here we go. Here we go.
好了 各位
Okay, everybody.
嗯...眼睛明亮点 都笑起来
Um... Bright eyes, and let's see those chompers.
惊喜
Surprise!
我的天啦
Jesus H. Christ!
他们都在里面
They're all in there!
我的意思是 我..我..我他妈看见彼得·麦哲伦了
I mean, I-- I-- I saw Peter fucking Magillan.
...还有他妈的悉德
...Fucking Cyd.
杰夫·格林威 我的意思是 我操
Jeff Greenway. I mean, fuck me.
我...我本来以为应该是...
I-- I thought it was supposed to be a--
-你知道 吃点牛排聊聊天就完事了  -瑞亚觉得那样会很好
-You know, a steak and a chat. -Rhea thought it would be nice.
好吧...
Well...
我们可以进去了吗
Shall we?
哇
Wow.
是的 看那个 我觉得那是...
Yeah, look at that. I think that's...
也许是"丹佛纪事报"
maybe the Denver Chronicle.
我在那里实习
I interned there.
一切还好吗
Everything okay?
嗯 是...
Yeah. It's--
消息传开了 说我在这里
Word got around that I'm over here
剧组里的演员都非常生气
and people from the play are super-pissed.
别担心 别担心 我们会搞定的 好吗
Don't worry, don't worry. We'll figure it out. Yeah?
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
所以 这实际上是一个非常棘手的
So, this was actually a pretty tough situation
分布情况
with the distribution,
-但是我父亲做的很棒...  -有没有人告诉过你
-but my dad did this amazing-- -Has anyone ever told you
你在谈论你父亲方面...谈了很多
that you talk about your dad, like... a lot?
好吧....
Okay....
不 我认为他们没告诉过我
No, I don't think they have.
我不是想讨人嫌
I wasn't trying to be nasty,
我只是指出一些情况
I was just pointing something out.
不 没关系 他..只不过 他是我们生活中的
No, it's cool, he's-- he's just a major presence
一个重要人物
in our lives.
你想跟他打招呼吗
Do you want to say hi?
-好的 好啊  -好吗 好吗
-Okay. Yeah. -Yeah? Yeah.
-我的意思是 他看起来有点忙  -我们走吧 不 不 不
-I mean, he looks kind of busy. -Let's go. Yeah, no, no, no.
-我要你见见我爸  -好的
-I want you to meet my dad. -Okay.
他会喜欢你的
He's gonna love you.
我有一个提议给你
I've got a proposition for you.
-是吗  -嗯
- Yeah? -Yeah.
那 我们有这样一个机会
So, we've got this opportunity
可以让你在经济上参与威拉的演出
for you to become involved financially in Willa's play,
我不知道你有没有一直听人说起
which I don't know if you've been hearing,
但是反响很棒
but the buzz is excellent.
你明白吧
You know?
所以 我真的很想和你谈谈
So, I'd really like to talk to you about that,
如果我能 只是 你知道……
if I could. Just, you know... ...
嘿 老爸 这位是詹妮弗
Hey, Dad. This is Jennifer.
你好
Hi.
很高兴认识你
Pleasure to meet you.
我也很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you, too.
嗯 也恭喜你 太棒了
Yeah, and congratulations, too. This is so awesome.
-谢谢  -嗯
-Thank you. -Yeah.
詹妮弗真的很棒 而且...
Jennifer's really amazing, and...
谢谢
Thanks.
她在剧院工作
She's in theatre.
嗯 也不算是
Well, not really.
好吧...我的意思是 你就是是 你是...
Well... I mean, you are. You are...
你就是
You are.
总之 这太棒了
Anyways, this is so awesome.
嗯 是的
Yes, it is.
我...
I...
我真的要去...
I should really mingle...
-很高兴认识你  -嗯
-So good to meet you. -Yeah.
看到肯德尔的最新女友了吗
Seen Kendall's latest?
...嗯
...Yeah.
其蠢如猪啊
Mind like a balloon.
嘿 你想...
Hey, you wanna...
你想今晚和平休战吗
You wanna call a truce for tonight?
好的
Okay.
我有东西给你
I got you something.
谢谢
Thank you.
很棒
Nice.
很漂亮的房子
Nice houses.
-是的 这些...  -很美
- Yeah, these are... -Lovely.
这些是我们的房子 爸爸
These are our houses, Dad.
-这些都是我们的  -真的吗
-They're all ours. -Really?
是啊 马里布
Yeah. Malibu.
你还记得...
You remember...
[纪念册]做得很好
Quality work.
不太喜欢过去 是吗
Don't like the past too much?
喜欢 喜欢
I do. I do.
只是...只是太多回忆了
It's...it's just there's so much of it.
未来才是真实的 但是...
The future is real, but...
过去 嗯...
the past, well, it's...
是啊 嗯...
Yeah. Um...
都是虚构的
It's all made up.
嗯...这次感觉很不好
It's, um... bad this time.
她不喝酒...
She doesn't drink...
...她有我的联络人信息
...She's got my contacts
每个人都来到了这里
and everyone, everyone is here.
而我什么都不知道
And I didn't know a thing.
是啊
Yeah.
她很保守 你知道吗
She's blue, you know?
她很自由
She's liberal.
是的 但是 我也是啊
Well, yeah, but so am I.
-是的 但是你他妈的懂的  -有点...
-Yeah, but you fucking get it. -Kinda--
你他妈的懂的 你知道吧
You fucking get it. You know?
我的意思是 她告诉我她喝了酒
I mean, she told me she drank.
我和她喝了威士忌
I shared a whisky with her.
欲擒故纵的挑逗
Prick tease.
我们不再用这个词了
We don't use that anymore.
嗯 我知道 我知道
Yeah. I know, I know.
各种各样有用的词就这样他妈的消失了
All sorts of useful fucking words have gone that way.
我很担心
I'm worried.
-别担心 爸  -是...
-Don't worry, Dad. -Is it--
我说对了吗
Have I got it right?
因为...
'Cause...
你很聪明 你很聪明
You're smart. You are smart.
-我...  -抱歉 打扰了
-I-- 'Scuse me, sorry to interrupt.
只是想 嗯 问你一件事
Just wanted to, um, ask you something
-关于今晚的程序  -好的
-about the procedures tonight. -Sure.
-关于蛋糕的问题  -耶耶耶 不 我...
-Question about cake. -Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, I...
-我得去撒尿  -好的
- I gotta go to the pisser. -Okay.
-厕所在哪儿  -就在...我想应该是那边
-Where is it? -Just-- I think it's that way.
嘿
Hey.
洛根叔公
Uncle Logs.
嘿 我只是...
Hey, I just--
我只是想说"祝你今晚开心"
I just wanted to say "Happy Night."
我不知道...
I don't know...
我不知道 我只是想...
I don't know. I just wanted to...
可能是我已经走到路的尽头了
It may be that I've reached the end of the road
就...而言...就...
in terms of-- of-- of like...
什么
What?
我爷爷说得很清楚了
My grandpa has made it clear
如果我想确保自己的未来
that if I want to secure my future,
那么我得切断和你的链接 协商一下"格雷格退出"
then I need to sever my links. Negotiate a bit of a "Grexit."
他现在提出的吗
Did he now?
很荣幸 嗯...
It has been a pleasure, um...
工作...和你一起工作 我学到了很多东西
work-- doing business with you, and I've learned a lot.
我希望 嗯...
And I hope that, um...
我希望我也带来了一些东西
I hope that I brought something to the table, too.
我喜欢你 格雷格
I like you, Greg.
好...好的 嗯
O-- Okay. Right.
真的 我喜欢你
I do. I like you.
他怎么说的
What did he say?
他威胁要把我踢出遗产受益人
He threatened to cut me off.
他不会那样做的
He won't do that.
他太他妈的胆小了
He's too much of a fucking coward.
所以他的一生才会毫无意义
That's why his whole life has amounted to nothing.
但是 你知道吗 最终取决于你 孩子
But you know, in the end, it's up to you, kiddo.
是啊
Yeah.
有趣的叔公...
Uncle Fun...
还是脾气暴躁的爷爷
or Grandpa Grumps.
因此 我特此召集新成立的
So, I hereby convene the meeting of the newly formed
"我们他妈的该怎么办"委员会的会议
"What the Fuck are We Gonna Do" committee.
那 我们向韦塞尔先生提出了第二次恩威并施的提议
So we made the second threat slash offer to Mr. Weissel
-他拒绝了  -拒绝了什么条件
-and he said no. -To what?
他对任何条件都拒绝
He said no to everything.
我们提出给2000万美元 他一点也没动心
We offered 20 million dollars. Didn't flinch.
丝毫不担心他会承担的法律诉讼成本
No fear of the cost of legal action.
根本没有和我们达成协议的欲望
Zero appetite to settle.
我们要求他开个价 任何价
We asked for a number. Any number.
显然 他没有开价  -没有开价吗
Apparently, this is no number. -There's no number?
很明显 背后有些事情正在发生
And there's obviously something going on under the water.
-我们认为他背后有支持者  -谁
-We think he has a backer? -Who?
任何对韦斯达怀恨在心的人都有可能
Could be anyone who has a grudge against Waystar.
找本电话簿来 我的意思是 清单很长的
Get a phone book. I mean, it's a very long list.
一切都有可能曝光出来 影子日志
It's all likely to come out: the shadow logs,
-保密协议 像多米诺骨牌一样  -我的天啦
- NDA, domino unraveling. -Mother!
事态呈螺旋状上升 发展得很快
It's spiraling. It's moving fast.
我们听到了黄鼠狼[和韦塞尔谐音]的声音 黄鼠狼正在协商上电视
We hear the weasel. The weasel is negotiating to go on TV
-然后倾吐他的心声 是啊  -我操
- and spill his guts. Yeah. -Fuck.
-后果会很严重  -我操
-It's gonna be huge. -Fuck.
会把天都捅漏
It's gonna blow wide open.
任何总裁任命都无济于事
Sour any CEO announcement.
新人会被撕成碎片
The new face is gonna get ripped to shreds.
短期问题是
Short term question is:
我们...什么时候告诉他 我们今晚告诉他吗
When... do we tell him? Do we tell him tonight?
有谁想在夜晚结束之前
Anyone want to end the night
当"地板上的野猪"吗
with a round of Boar on the Floor?
重点是 我的意思是...
Big picture, I mean...
黄鼠狼是一种生死存亡的威胁
The weasel is an existential threat.
好的
Okay.
我们给他放一晚上的假
We give him the night off.
让他享受今晚 我们明天告诉他
Let him enjoy the night. We'll tell him tomorrow.
-这样吗   -嗯
-Yeah? -Yeah.
如果我必须告诉他 是你做的决定
And if I had to tell him you made the call,
你还是愿意做这个决定吗
would you still be happy with the call?
就这样决定了
That's the call.
...晚上好 各位
...Good evening, everyone.
很高兴大家今晚聚在这里
It's a pleasure to have you here tonight
纪念我父亲的生活和工作
to honor my dad's life and work.
那 当瑞亚计划这个活动时 她请我帮她
So, when Rhea was planning this, she asked me to help out
在...嗯 在某些情调方面做一点...
with, um... with a little tribute to the certain...
贡献
flavor.
经过一番说服之后 嗯
And after a lot of convincing, well...
我们来了
Here we are.
他要脱衣服吗
Is he about to strip?
-只是希望大家了解 我不是专业人士  -我想他是在舞台上
-Just remember I'm not a professional. -Think he's going to masturbate
对着爸爸的一张照片打飞机
onstage to a photo of Dad.
我儿子斯奎格为我准备了这个节拍
My boy Squiggle cooked up this beat for me.
一起来听听
Check it.
♪ 出生于北岸 东边的国王 ♪
♪ Born on the North Bank King of the East Side ♪
♪ 五十年硬朗 摇摆中坚强 ♪
♪ Fifty years strong now He's rollin' in a sick ride ♪
♪ 手工的西装 横扫那战场 ♪
♪ Handmade suits Raking in loot ♪
♪ 五星的上将 最佳的敬仰 哟 ♪  -不
♪ Five star general Y'all best salute, yo ♪ -No.
-不-老天啊 不  -天哪
-No. Jesus, no. No. -My God!
匪帮说唱小肯[N.W.A. 康普顿的嘻哈音乐团体]
Ken.W.A.
我的意思是...太辣眼睛了
I mean it's... it is burning my eyes,
但是我无法移开视线
but I cannot look away.
♪ L到OG ♪
♪ L to the OG ♪
♪ 老爹创世纪 ♪
♪ Dude be the OG ♪
♪ A-N 他玩弄全城 ♪
♪ A-N he playin' ♪
♪ 是个职业超人 看 ♪
♪ Playin' like a pro, see ♪
♪ L到OG ♪
♪ L to the OG ♪
♪ 老爹创世纪 ♪
♪ Dude be the OG ♪
♪ A-N 他玩弄全城 ♪
♪ A-N he playin' ♪
♪ 是个职业超人 ♪
♪ Playin' like a pro ♪
气氛再热烈点
Make some noise!
♪ 最高的等级 最贵的尚品 ♪
♪ A1 ratings, 80K wine ♪
♪ 永远不要停 宝贝 他妈的时光老人 兄弟 ♪
♪ Never gonna stop, baby Fuck father time, bro ♪
♪ 不要想太多 地狱我经历过 ♪
♪ Don't get it twisted I've been through hell ♪
♪ 但自从我站起 老爸 我仍然很好活着 ♪
♪ But since I stan Dad I'm alive and well ♪
♪ 观点塑造者 新闻创造者 ♪
♪ Shaper of views Creator of news ♪
♪ 子女的慈父 承担了职责 ♪
♪ Father of many Paid all his dues ♪
♪ 不要有企图 对国王爆粗 ♪
♪ So don't try to run Your mouth at the king ♪
♪ 仰起你小脸 婊子 亲吻那指环 ♪
♪ Just pucker up, bitch And go kiss the ring ♪
♪ L到OG ♪
♪ L to the OG ♪
♪ 老爹创世纪 ♪
♪ Dude be the OG ♪
♪ A-N 他玩弄全城 ♪
♪ A-N he playin' ♪
气氛再热烈点
Make some noise!
♪ 我说L 你们说OG ♪
♪ When I say L, you say OG ♪
♪ L到... ♪
♪ L to the... ♪
♪ L到... ♪  -♪ OG ♪
♪ L to the... ♪ -♪ OG ♪
- ♪ L到... ♪  -你得让他停下来
-♪ L to the... ♪ -You need to stop this.
- ♪ L到... ♪  - ♪ OG ♪
-♪ L to the... ♪ -♪ OG ♪
♪ L到... ♪
♪ L to the... ♪
♪ L到他妈屌爆的OG ♪
♪ L to the motherfucking OG ♪
我觉得这可能是公司的末日
I think this might be the end of the company.
我们可能会陷入一个我们永远无法摆脱的
We might get sucked into a black hole of embarrassment
尴尬的黑洞
that we never get out of.
这里是他妈的敦提
Dundee in the motherfucking house.
请各位注意
If I can get your attention.
以下是对这位传奇人物洛根·罗伊的一些赞誉
Some appreciations of the man, the legend, Logan Roy.
嘿 老爸 大家好
Hey, Dad. Hey, everybody.
嗯...
Um...
是的 你们都知道我经历过起起落落...
Yeah, you all know that I've had my ups and downs...
可以这么说
you could say.
但是 嗯...
And, um...
你们可能不知道的是 我父亲是那个
What you might not know is that my dad has been the one
在我最低潮的时刻来见我的人...
who's been to meet me at my lowest moments...
嘿 抱歉打扰 你还记得爱德华吗
Hey, sorry to interrupt. You remember Eduard?
只是想祝贺你一辈子都这么厉害
Just wanna say congrats on a lifetime of kicking ass.
谢谢 我还没死呢
Thanks. I'm not dead yet.
嗯...还有 我给你准备了一份礼物 实际上我们给你准备了一份礼物
Um... Also, I got you a present. We actually got you a present.
我们买下了赫斯队
We bought the Hearts.
洛根 周年快乐...
Logan, happy anniversary...
赫斯队
The Hearts? !
赫斯足球俱乐部吗
Hearts Football Club? !
-为什么  -为什么...因为是赫斯队啊
-Why? -Why-- Because it's the Hearts.
是你喜欢的球队
It's your team.
-我是希伯队  -你是希伯队粉丝吗
-I'm Hibs. -You're Hibs?
真的吗
Really?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我以为你是赫斯队 我很确定 爸爸
I thought you were Hearts. I'm pretty sure, Dad.
你知道吗 也许你是对的
You know, maybe you're right.
我怎么知道我他妈这辈子支持哪个球队
How would I know what team I supported all my fucking life?
我的意思是 也许我支持基马诺克队
I mean, maybe I support Kilmarnock.
还是法克尔切斯特流浪者队
Or Fucklechester Rangers?
我的意思是 我他妈怎么可能知道
I mean, how can I fucking possibly fucking know?
希望我的话能够安慰到你 我不擅长买礼物
If it's any consolation, I'm horrible at gift buying.
是啊 总是买到错误的东西
Yeah. Always get the wrong thing.
嘿 是我 看看
Hey, it's me. Watch it.
我能说什么 恭喜一千年...
What can I say? Congrats on a thousand years...
-嘿  -嘿 小西
-Hey. -Hey, Shiv.
听着 我...我真的...我真的...
Listen, I-- I really-- I really am...
在想这个问题 瑞亚
wondering about this. Rhea.
爸 听我说 你必须做你觉得正确的事情
Dad. Listen. You gotta do what you think is right.
好吗 就是这样的
Yeah? That's all there is.
她最合适 就目前而言 她最合适
And she's the one. For now, she's the one.
嘿 老爸 恭喜
Hey, Dad. Congrats!
听着 我知道你讨厌所有这些废话
Look, I know how you hate all this bullshit,
所以 我就只说一句..."去你的 老爸"
so I'll just say... "Fuck you, Dad,"
我希望我们是在喝酒 而不是在这里
and I wish we were having wine instead of being here
和所有这些害怕你的人在一起
with all these people who are scared of you.
相信你的直觉 好吗
Just trust your gut. Yeah?
你不会因为感情
You can't give it to me
把接班人位置给我或者任何人
or anyone else because of sentiment.
你自己心里清楚
You know that.
谢谢你 亲爱的
Thank you, darling.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯
Yeah.
还有30秒到您上台 罗伊先生
30 seconds to VT, Mr. Roy.
你没事吧
You all right?
是不是...是不是太过了
Was it-- Was it all too much?
我不喜欢惊喜
I'm not crazy about surprises.
我没想到会有这么多友好的面孔
I wasn't expecting so many friendly faces.
我的意思是 你们把我打败了 你们这些混蛋
I mean, you got me, you bastards.
你们知道吗 你们真的把我打败了
You know, you really got me.
但是说真的 我很感动
But seriously, no. I'm touched.
嗯...
Um...
有人说 我对工作很执着
Some people say that I'm wedded to my work.
随便问我的哪个妻子就知道了
Just ask any of my wives.
但是 我对韦斯达集团在过去的50年中
But I'm amazed at what Waystar has achieved
取得的成就感到惊讶
over the last 50 years.
我为我的家人感到骄傲 他们帮助我实现了这样的成就
And I'm proud of my family, who have helped me get here.
在我看来 掌舵了50年之后 现在...
And it seems to me that now, after 50 years at the helm...
现在也许是一个好时机 思考...
now might be a smart time to think about...
谁能帮我续写新的篇章
who will help me write the next chapter.
我会在今晚适当的时候宣布
I'm gonna announce tonight, in due course,
我将任命...
I shall be appointing...
瑞亚·贾瑞尔...
Rhea Jarrell...
作为我的集团总裁
as my chief executive officer.
以上是我的声明
Statement to follow.
嘿 你唱的很带劲啊
Hey! That was pretty intense.
是啊
Yeah.
你 嗯...
You, um...
你说了...你说了很多"太棒了"
You said-- You said "awesome" a lot.
什么
What?
你说了很多"太棒了"
You said "awesome" a lot
你和我爸说话的时候
when you were talking to my dad.
是吗 好吧 我没留意到
Did I? Okay. I didn't notice that.
没关系 只是...只是很有趣
It's fine. It was just-- It was funny.
你冷得瑟瑟发抖 我...我帮你拿你的外套吧
You're freezing. Let me-- Let me get your coat.
-我马上回来  -好的
-I'll be right back. -Okay.
嘿 可以让珍妮佛搭第一班飞机离开这里吗
Hey, can we get Jennifer on the first flight outta here?
当然可以 一切还好吗
Sure thing. Everything okay?
...是啊 挺好
...Yeah. Good.
也许...嘿 嘿 托尼
Maybe-- Hey. Hey, Tony.
-也许吧...让她知道我可能有事  -好的
-Maybe, um... let her know I might be tied up. -Okay.
不好意思
Excuse me.
今晚不错吧
Nice night?.
你还好吗
You okay?
你要隐退的事 你一点也没告诉我 为什么
You told me nothing about you stepping aside. Why?
我道歉
I apologize.
你让我伤心了
You broke something here.
我不喜欢你的想法...
I didn't like it...
你告诉我 我应该卖掉我的公司的时候
when you told me that I should sell my company.
你听到了你想听的话
You hear what you wanna hear,
但是你却因为我没过说的话而惩罚我
then you punish me for something I didn't say.
我可能做了一些错误的判断
I may have made some misjudgments.
你很粗心
You're careless.
-你对我很粗心  -玛西娅
-You've been careless of me. -Marcia.
我很无聊 你让我感到无聊
I'm bored. You are boring me.
对不起 罗伊先生 现在是时候揭匾了
Excuse me, it's time for the plaque now, Mr. Roy.
-我要走了  -玛西娅
-I'm going. -Marcia.
别他妈犯傻 马上揭匾了
Don't be fucking stupid. It's a plaque.
老天呀 我会错过揭匾的 对吗
God forbid, I will miss the plaque. Right?
你那闪亮的小墓碑
Your shiny little gravestone.
看来你将不得不独自面对自己的清算了
Guess you'll have to face your reckoning alone.
妈妈会厌恶这一切的
Mother would have hated all this.
还有被你称之为新闻的垃圾
And that trash you call news.
妈妈去世的时候 你才五岁...
Now, we last saw her when you were five...
我也才四岁...
and I was four...
但是 你居然知道她会认可
but you know what kind of journalism
什么样的新闻
she would've approved of?
我知道她永远不会认可你现在的样子
I know she never would've approved of what you've become.
什么样子 做你的饭票的样子吗
What? Your meal ticket?
我只是很惊讶你居然还活着
I'm just surprised you're still standing.
要是换了别人 肯定早就羞死了
Any other man would've died from the shame.
很难知道
It's hard to know
哪一个的毒性更大
which is more toxic:
是你的新闻媒体还是你的游轮部门
your news outlets or your cruise division.
这么多年来 一直为罗丝而自责
All those years blaming yourself for Rose.
-我没兴趣谈这个  -那真的不是你的错
-I'm not interested. -That really wasn't your fault.
不过 这个...
This, though...
这个是你的错
This is your fault.
这个狗屎帝国
This empire of shit.
是时候偿还一切了
Time to pay up.
女士们 先生们 正式揭幕
Ladies and gentlemen, it is that time.
海伦·埃尔斯佩思·罗伊学院
The Helen Elspeth Roy College!
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠